[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wolves can live in snowy areas at certain times of the year?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country is the largest consumer of gold in the world?", "correct_answer": "India", "incorrect_answers": ["South Africa", "United Arab Emirates", "China"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Diner actor has turned down lead roles in Pulp Fiction, 48 Hrs, The Untouchables, Platoon, and Beverly Hills Cop.", "correct_answer": "Mickey Rourke", "incorrect_answers": ["Bruce Willis", "Micheal Biehn", "Charlie Sheen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Hiroo Onoda?", "correct_answer": "The last Japanese casualty from World War II", "incorrect_answers": ["The founder of Mazda", "This is the real name of Tojo.", "The Japanese fisherman who first sees Godzilla in the movie of the same name"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Elvira Wayans was a writer on what Damon Wayans television show?", "correct_answer": "My Wife and Kids", "incorrect_answers": ["In Living Color", "House of Payne", "My Brothers Keeper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular nursery rhyme was written by author and editor Sarah Josepha Hale, who campaigned for making Thanksgiving a national holiday in the US?", "correct_answer": "Mary Had a Little Lamb", "incorrect_answers": ["Peter Peter Pumpkin Eater", "Baa Baa Black Sheep", "Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which company did Clarence Saunders found in 1916?", "correct_answer": "The Piggly Wiggly", "incorrect_answers": ["Kentucky Fried Chicken", "Dominos Pizza", "Burger King"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Decaffeinated coffee contains no caffeine.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Princess Fionas only way to break the curse and turn back to her original form in the 2001 animated comedy Shrek?", "correct_answer": "Being kissed by her true love", "incorrect_answers": ["Help somebody that she really hates", "Drink a magic potion", "Perform a belly dance in front of the three blind mice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays Indiana Jones friend, Markus Brody, who is a museum curator?", "correct_answer": "Denholm Elliot", "incorrect_answers": ["Joseph Elbry", "George Roudolph", "Henry Jackson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Cairo, Indiana Jones is racing against the Nazis to find the Ark first. He enlists his Egyptian friend to help. What is his name?", "correct_answer": "Sallah", "incorrect_answers": ["Sultan", "Sabre", "Steve"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following groups of fruits are considered low-acid fruits?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Cherries, sweet peaches, sweet plums", "Blueberries, huckleberries, strawberries", "Mangos, elderberries, olives, fresh figs"]}]